BYEONGJOO AHN

Homepage: https://byeongjooahn.github.io/ \$ Email: byeongjoo@apple.com

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in computational imaging, computer vision, and computer graphics. I am interested in identifying visible hints offered by our physical surroundings such as interreflections, and developing imaging systems extending the visibility far beyond human ability such as the reconstruction of objects that are not in the direct line of sight or those with strong self-occlusions.

EDUCATION

Carnegie Mellon University

Pittsburgh, PA

Ph.D. in Electrical and Computer Engineering

2017 - 2023

Advisors: Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan and Ioannis Gkioulekas Thesis: "Full-surround 3D Reconstruction using Kaleidoscopes"

Thesis Committee: Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan (CMU), Ioannis Gkioulekas (CMU),

Manmohan Chandraker (UCSD), Shree K. Nayar (Columbia)

Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

M.S. in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

2012 - 2014

Advisor: Kyoung Mu Lee

Thesis: "Occlusion-Aware Motion Deblurring for Bilayer Scenes"

Outstanding Thesis Award

Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering

Summa Cum Laude

2008 - 2012

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Apple Seattle, WA

Research Scientist Jan. 2024 – Present

Apple Seattle, WA

Research Intern with Rick Chang and Karren Yang

Jan. 2023 – Sep. 2023

Snap Inc. (Remote) New York, NY

Research Intern with Shree K. Nayar and Jian Wang May. 2020 – Aug. 2020

Carnegie Mellon University Pittsburgh, PA

Research Assistant Sep. 2017 – Dec. 2023

Korea Institute of Science and Technology Seoul, Korea

Research Scientist Mar. 2014 – Aug. 2017

HP Labs

Palo Alto, CA

Intern with Irwin Sobel Jan. 2012 – Feb. 2012

PUBLICATIONS

"Novel-view Acoustic Synthesis From 3D Reconstructed Rooms"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Karren Yang, Brian Hamilton, Jonathan Sheaffer, Anurag Ranjan, Miguel Sarabia, Oncel Tuzel, Jen-Hao Rick Chang *Interspeech*, 2024

"Neural Kaleidoscopic Space Sculpting"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Michael De Zeeuw, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2023

"Kaleidoscopic Structured Light"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *ACM Transactions on Graphics (Proc. SIGGRAPH ASIA)*, 2021

"Convolutional Approximations to the General Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging Operator"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Akshat Dave, Ashok Veeraraghavan, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2019 (Oral Presentation)

"Occlusion-Aware Video Deblurring with a New Layered Blur Model"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Tae Hyun Kim, Wonsik Kim, Kyoung Mu Lee *arXiv preprint arXiv:1611.09572*, 2016

"Reduced Illumination Patterns for Acquisition of Specular and Diffuse Normal Maps"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Junghyun Cho, Taekyung Yoo, Ig-Jae Kim

ACM SIGGRAPH ASIA Poster, 2016

"Dynamic Scene Deblurring"

Tae Hyun Kim, **Byeongjoo Ahn**, Kyoung Mu Lee

IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2013

AWARDS AND HONORS Top Reviewer, NeurIPS 2022 2022 **Doctoral Study Abroad Scholarship**, Korea Foundation for Advanced Studies 2017 Fulbright Graduate Study Award (gratefully declined), Fulbright 2017 Best Poster Award, KIST R&D EXPO 2014 Outstanding Thesis Award, Department of EECS, Seoul National University 2014 Honorable Mention Award, Samsung Humantech Paper Award 2014 Graduate Scholarship, Kwanjeong Educational Foundation 2012 **Presidential Science Scholarship**, Korea Student Aid Foundation 2008

TEACHING

Teaching Assistant, Carnegie Mellon University

- · 15-463/663/862 Computational Photography
- · Recitation for 18-290 Signals and Systems

Fall 2020

Spring 2019, 2020

SERVICES

Area Chair, NeurIPS 2024

Program Committee, ICCP (2023, 2024)

Reviewer, CVPR (2019, 2020, 2021, 2022, 2023, 2024), ICCV (2019, 2021, 2023), ECCV (2020, 2024), BMVC (2019), ICLR (2022), NeurIPS (2022, 2023), SIGGRAPH (2022), SIGGRAPH ASIA (2023), TIP (2022–), TCI (2024)

Student Volunteer, ACCV 2012, ICCP 2021

Volunteer, Camera Building Workshop as part of Gelfand Outreach Program at CMU (2019)

Mentor, CMU AI Mentoring Program (2021)

Last updated: Jun 5, 2024